Artur Babiński

Electronics Technician



Personal Info

Date of birth

1996-06-09

Email

artur.babinski.g@gmail.com

Phone

730260290

GitHub

github.com/quenrythane/

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/artur-babinski

Skills

Python, Git, MySQL

Reading technical documentation

Knowledge of Windows and Linux (running an Ubuntu server on AWS EC2)

Very well knowledge of the construction and operation of computers

Logical and analytical thinking

Being a team player

Communication Skills

Effectively obtain information in order to solve the encountered problems

Eagerness to learn and constantly improve

yourself

Inquisitiveness, perceptiveness MS Office: especially Excel

Languages

Polish - native English - B2

Hobby

Programming, Artificial Intelligence, Data Science, Electronics, Robotics, Cyber-Security, Web3

Business Psychology, Behavioral Psychology, Cognitive Science

I am a person who is fascinated by technological achievements, especially robotics and artificial intelligence solutions.

I love to get to know and learn about how technical solutions work and what I can do with them. That is why I started to be interested in and explore the secrets of electronics, and then programming. The results of my experience give me visible and tangible results, which motivate me even more to work.

Work History

2021-10

AV systems fitter

- 2022-01

Image Recording Solutions Pomorze Sp. z.o.o., Gdańsk

Implementation of audiovisual systems in the famous Dom Zdrojowy Gdańsk Hevelianum:

Installation of drop-down screens, projectors, 100-inch interactive monitors, control

panels, wall-mounted speakers and overhead ceiling speakers.

Installation of rack cabinets and devices in cabinets, amplifiers, switches, transmitters, receivers, connection of all equipment

2017-06

Magic camps counselor

- present

Quatromondis HUGO YORCK Jakub Jędrzejak, Poland

Transpost and care for children aged 8-18.

Preparing and conducting magic classes (wizard chess club, magic duels, potions, Quidditch and many others),

Inventing, preparing, organizing and lead fictional games, including author's games

Solving current problems of children, supporting, educating and raising them, ensuring safety, having fun, helping to make friends, caring for bonds in the group and proper nutrition of children.

Preparing and conducting evening events such as disguise shows, singing, dancing and knowledge competitions

2014-12

Praktykant

- 2015-01

TELKOM-TELMOR, Gdańsk

Assembly of SMD, SMT, THT electronic components, soldering, operation of soldering machines, production antenna.

Education

2018-09 IT specialist

- 2020-06

Cosinus

2016-10

Economy

- 2017-05

Gdańsk University of Technology

2012-09

Electronics Technician

- 2016-05

Complex of Secondary Technical Schools of Communication

Technology

Certificates

Dyplom Technika Elektronika (E06: praktyczny 100%, E20 praktyczny 79%)

Certyfikat IPC - Association Connecting Electronics Industries

33-hour course on the basics of mechatronics and robotics